KATIE KRUKOFF

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Service-Orientated professional with over five years of demonstrated customer service experience. Core competencies include excellent interpersonal skills, self-motivation, attention to detail, and the ability to multi-task. Excellent communication and time management skills. Handles tasks with accuracy and efficiency.

WORK HISTORY

Operations Support/ Customer Service – 01/2022- Current Silver Gold Bull, Calgary, AB

- Answering incoming emails and phone calls regarding customer accounts and shipments
- Track and solve issues that arise regarding customers' shipments
- Monitor live market of Silver and Gold
- Handle customer facing inventory issues
- Trusted with highly classified information and goods
- Assist other departments with tasks that arise

Administrative Assistant/ Accounts Receivable, - 08/2022- 01/2023 Diversified Staffing Services, Calgary, AB

- Answer Phone calls/ Emails and redirect to appropriate parties
- Send Invoices
- Handle AR inbox and inquires
- Assist with schedules and interviews
- Completed reference checks
- Reformatted resumes and files
- Assist with other departments with tasks that arise
- Proficient with Microsoft Office, CRM and Adobe

Sales Consultant, 08/2021 - 08/2022

Lindt, Calgary, AB

- Educate customers in the world of chocolate
- Handle inquires about product and sales
- Manage staff and tasks that need to be completed
- Push sales by paying attention to detail and recommending other products and promotions.

Sales and Marketing Consultant, 06/2020 - 03/2021

Zingaro Marketing, Calgary, AB

- Face to face marketing representing a wide range of clients through corporate events
- Assisting in training for event management, including event set up and take down
- Provided exceptional customer service through product knowledge and customer care
- Maintained scheduling and event calendars.

Sales Consultant, 09/2018 - 03/2020

Muge, Calgary, AB

- Managed incoming and outgoing packages and payments
- Answered telephones and gave information to clients, took messages, and transferred calls to appropriate departments
- Set up and managed paper and electronic filing systems, recorded information, updated paperwork and maintained documents

0

Calgary, AB T2A



403-771-4079



Katiekrukoff@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Ability to multi-task and meet deadlines
- Microsoft Office
- CRM
- Adobe
- Strong Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- Strong attention to Detail
- Passionate and Driven for Success
- Team Cooperation
- Time management Skills
- Exceeding Customer and company
 Expectations

- Provided proper account information
- Performed database management and Word processing
- Maintained schedule and event calendars.

Sales Consultant, 09/2017 - 03/2020

Plato's Closet NE, Calgary, AB

- Used various applications, such as POC and word processing
- Train and assist staff
- Managed Social media platform (Instagram)
- Answered phones and gave information to clients, took messages, and transferred calls to appropriate departments.

Poll Clerk, 10/2019 - 10/2019

Provincial Election

- Created, maintained and entered information for visitors
- Greeted visitors and handled their inquiries or directed them to the appropriate persons according to their needs
- Located and attached appropriate files to incoming inquires.

Poll Clerk, 10/2017 - 10/2017

Municipal Election

- Created, maintained and entered information for visitors
- Greeted visitors and handled their inquiries or directed them to the appropriate persons according to their needs
- Located and attached appropriate files to incoming inquires.

02/2017 - 10/2017

Calaway Live Cast, Calaway Park, Calgary, AB

- Established work procedures or schedules and keep track of the daily work
- Manage projects
- Greeted visitors
- Maintained a clean and safe performance space.

EDUCATION

Directory, Health Care Studies, HCA

MaKami College Inc - Calgary, AB